{
    "weeklyContestStatus": "on",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Giving a student extra homework after they misbehave in class is an example of:",
            "options": {
                "A": "Positive Reinforcement",
                "B": "Negative Punishment",
                "C": "Positive Punishment",
                "D": "Negative Reinforcement"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "Usmael's parents believe in his uniqueness and strength as an individual. They feel much more confident about himâ€”as if he is really growing and reaching his full potential. The therapist being described most likely follows a:",
            "options": {
                "A": "Cognitive perspective",
                "B": "Socio-cultural perspective",
                "C": "Biological perspective",
                "D": "Humanistic perspective"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "Coca-Cola Company gave a surprise gift bonus for the workers for their outstanding performance of the year. Which one of the schedules of reinforcement is indicated above?",
            "options": {
                "A": "Variable interval",
                "B": "Fixed ratio",
                "C": "Fixed interval",
                "D": "Variable ratio"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "Acquiring a fear of light because you saw someone else getting shocked when the light came on is an example of:",
            "options": {
                "A": "Social learning",
                "B": "Classical Learning",
                "C": "Instrumental Learning",
                "D": "Involuntary learning"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "Getahun got sick after he ate shero wate in the cafeteria. Now he feels sick when he looks at shero and all bean products. This illustrates:",
            "options": {
                "A": "Spontaneous recovery",
                "B": "Stimulus Generalization",
                "C": "Modeling",
                "D": "Intermittent reinforcement"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "This field of psychology studies differences in behavior among individuals.",
            "options": {
                "A": "Counseling Psychology",
                "B": "Educational Psychology",
                "C": "Developmental Psychology",
                "D": "Personality Psychology"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "This field applies techniques and strategies to make learning take place in the most satisfactory way possible.",
            "options": {
                "A": "Counseling Psychology",
                "B": "Educational Psychology",
                "C": "Clinical Psychology",
                "D": "School Psychology"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "This field deals with the maturational development of people and their passage through the different stages of growth, from childhood to old age.",
            "options": {
                "A": "Developmental Psychology",
                "B": "Social Psychology",
                "C": "Forensic Psychology",
                "D": "Clinical Psychology"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "This field deals with less severe psychological problems.",
            "options": {
                "A": "Clinical Psychology",
                "B": "Counseling Psychology",
                "C": "Forensic Psychology",
                "D": "Social Psychology"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "This field studies the way we affect and are affected by others.",
            "options": {
                "A": "Developmental Psychology",
                "B": "Social Psychology",
                "C": "Clinical Psychology",
                "D": "Educational Psychology"
            },
            "correctAnswer": "B"
        }
    ]
}
